Preliminary Guide to the Charles Reinhart Management, Inc. Records, 1956-1992
American Dance Festival Archives
- Subject Files, 1956-1992
  - Nancy Hauser Review, Conversations/Correspondence with Hauser Co (Box 11)
  - Nancy Hauser Review, Miscellaneous Telephone Conversations (Box 11)
  - Nancy Hauser Review, Telephone Conversations with Endowment (Box 11)
  - Nancy Hauser Review, Letters Inquiring about Panel Decision (Box 11)
  - Nancy Hauser Review, Consultant Reports/Minutes of Meeting with Mini-Panel (Box 11)
  - Nancy Hauser Review, Corres. With Endowment and Drafts of Responses (Box 11)
  - Hauser "Party", Jan. 13, 1978 (Box 11)
  - CR/Hauser (Box 11)
  - Nancy Hauser Review, School/Artist Site Reports on Hauser Residencies (Box 11)
  - AIS Reports to Xerox and File, 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Chron File (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous Crap (Box 11)
  - Blank Contracts AIS (Box 11)
  - DMS Contracts, 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Dance Movement Specialists, Contracts, Dates, Assistants, Residency Info Sheet, and Other Crap (Box 11)
  - DMS Contract Forms, 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Project Management AIS, 1978 (Box 11)
  - Signed Agreements (Box 12)
  - Arizona, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Arizona Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Independent Contractor Statements for DMS, off list, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - California Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - California, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Connecticut, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Connecticut Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Florida Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Florida, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Georgia, 1981-1982 (Box 12)
  - Hawaii, 1980 (Box 12)
  - Hawaii, Phone Calls (Box 12)
  - Illinois Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Illinois, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Iowa, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Iowa Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Louisiana, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Louisiana Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Maine Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Maine, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Commonwealth Arts Council of The Northern Marianas (Box 12)
  - Massachusetts Phone Calls (Box 12)
  - Massachusetts, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Rod Rogers Dance Company, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 12)
  - The Massachusetts Council on the Arts and Humanities, Guide to Programs and Services, July 1, 1980-June 30, 1981 (Box 12)
  - Michigan, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Michigan Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Mississippi, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Mississippi Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Missouri Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Missouri, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Nebraska, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Nebraska Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - New Hampshire, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - New Hampshire Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - New Jersey Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - New Jersey, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - New Mexico, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - New Mexico Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - New York Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - The Alliance of New York State Arts Councils, Inc., Something for Everyone; Special Assistance Program, 1978 (Box 12)
  - New York, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - North Carolina, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - North Carolina Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - North Dakota, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - North Dakota Phone Calls, 1981 (Box 12)
  - Ohio, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Ohio Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Oregon Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Oregon, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Pennsylvania Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Pennsylvania, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Puerto Rico, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Puerto Rico Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Rhode Island, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Rhode Island Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Phone Calls, Michigan (Box 13)
  - Phone Calls, Minnesota (Box 13)
  - Phone Calls, MO (Box 13)
  - Missouri, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Nevada, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Phone Calls, NV (Box 13)
  - New Jersey, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Phone Calls, New Jersey (Box 13)
  - New Hampshire, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Phone Calls, New Hampshire (Box 13)
  - Phone Calls, NM (Box 13)
  - New Mexico, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Phone Calls. New York (Box 13)
  - New York, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Phone Calls, North Carolina (Box 13)
  - North Carolina, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Phone Calls, ND (Box 13)
  - North Dakota, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Phone Calls, Ohio (Box 13)
  - Ohio (Box 13)
  - Ohio, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Phone Calls-OR (Box 13)
  - Oregon, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Pennsylvania, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Phone Calls-Pennsylvania (Box 13)
  - Puerto Rico, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Phone Calls, Puerto Rico, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Rhode Island, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Phone Calls, Rhode Island (Box 13)
  - Phone Calls, SD (Box 13)
  - South Dakota, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Tennessee, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Phone Calls, TN (Box 13)
  - Phone Calls, UT (Box 13)
  - Utah, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Phone Calls, Vermont (Box 13)
  - Vermont, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Phone Calls, Virgin Islands (Box 13)
  - Virgin Islands, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - AIS Correspondence, Apr. 1979-June 30, 1979 (Box 14)
  - AIS Chronological File, Apr. 1, 1979-June 30, 1979 (Box 14)
  - AIS Chronological File, Corres, Jan. 1, 1979-Mar. 31, 1979 (Box 14)
  - AIS Chronological Correspondence, July 1, 1979-Dec. 31, 1979 (Box 14)
  - AIS Chron Correspondence, Jan 1, 1980-Mar. 31, 1980 (Box 14)
  - AIS Chronological File, Corres, July 1, 1980-Sept. 30, 1980 (Box 14)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Reports of NEA Consultants on Presently Participating Dance Companies and Dance Movement Specialists, 1976-1977 (Box 14)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Reports of NEA Consultants on Presently Participating Dance Companies and Dance Movement Specialists, 1976-1977 (Box 14)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Reports of NEA Consultants on Presently Participating Dance Companies and Dance Movement Specialists, 1976-1977 (Box 14)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Process, Dance Movement Specialists ReReview, Anthony-Woodbury, 1978-1979 (Box 14)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Process, Dance Companies, Acme-Utah Repertory Dance Theatre, 1978-1979 (Box 14)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Process, Supplementary Directory, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Process, Supplementary Directory, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Process, Supplementary Directory, Dance Movement Specialists Applicants: Diamond-Keystone, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Process, Supplemental Directory, Dance Movement Specialists Applicants: Schwartz-Williams, Dance Company Applicant: Nancy Hauser Dance Company, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Process, Supplemental Directory, Dance Movement Specialists Applicants: Lasansky-Pearson, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, All Review Reports, Dance Movement Specialists Applicants: Baum-Walton; Dance Companies Applicants: Frank Ashley Dance Company- Theatre Ballet of San Francisco; ReReviews: Barlin-Wing, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Process, Dance Movement Specialists Applicants: Baum-Walton, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Process, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
  - SAA's/Regional Coor., AIS, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
  - AIS Related Programs, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
  - AIS State Coordinators Meeting, Notre Dame, IN, July 16-18, 1975 (Box 14)
  - Company Statements, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
  - DMS Statements, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
  - In-School Coordinator Information Sheets, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
  - AIS/DC East Coast Coordination, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
  - Alabama, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
  - Arkansas, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
  - Arizona, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
  - California, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
  - Goleta Follow-Up (Box 15)
  - Connecticut, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
  - Delaware, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
  - Florida, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
  - Florida: Tom Watters (Box 15)
  - Hawaii, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
  - Illinois Phone Calls, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
  - Illinois, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
  - Indiana, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
  - Iowa, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
  - Kentucky (Box 15)
  - Louisiana, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
  - Maine, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
  - AIS, Wellesley, Mass., Mar. 1975 (Box 15)
  - Massachusetts, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
  - Contracts and Letters of Agreement, General Info and Correspondence (Box 15)
  - AIS/DC, Aug. 29, 1979 Memo, Residency Information Sheets, 1979-1980 (Box 15)
  - State Information, AIS Dance Component, 1979-1980 (Box 15)
  - Arizona Phone Calls (Box 15)
  - Arizona, 1979-1980 (Box 15)
  - Arkansas Phone Calls (Box 15)
  - Arkansas, 1979-1980 (Box 15)
  - California Phone Calls (Box 15)
  - California, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Connecticut Phone Calls (Box 16)
  - Connecticut, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Florida, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Florida Phone Calls (Box 16)
  - Hawaii Phone Calls (Box 16)
  - Hawaii, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Illinois, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Illinois Phone Calls (Box 16)
  - Iowa, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Louisiana Phone Calls (Box 16)
  - Louisiana, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Maine, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Maine Phone Calls (Box 16)
  - Massachusetts Phone Calls (Box 16)
  - Massachusetts, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Michigan, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Michigan Phone Calls (Box 16)
  - Mississippi, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Mississippi Phone Calls (Box 16)
  - Missouri, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Missouri Phone Calls (Box 16)
  - Nebraska Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 16)
  - Nebraska, 1980-1981 (Box 16)
  - New Hampshire, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - New Hampshire Phone Calls (Box 16)
  - New Jersey Phone Calls (Box 16)
  - New Jersey, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - New Mexico, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - New Mexico Phone Calls (Box 16)
  - New York, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - New York Phone Calls (Box 16)
  - City of Durham, 1980 (Box 16)
  - North Carolina (Box 16)
  - North Dakota, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - North Dakota Phone Calls (Box 16)
  - Ohio Phone Calls (Box 16)
  - Ohio, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Oregon, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Housing Files, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Housing Files, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Chuck Davis Proposals (Box 17)
  - AIS/Dance Component Contact Lists, Panel/Artists/Educators/SAA's (Box 17)
  - SAA AIS Grant Applications, 1975-1976 (Box 17)
  - Program Management, Artists in Schools, Participants List; Summer Workshop Registration Forms, 1977 (Box 17)
  - Program Management, Artists in Schools, Summer Workshop Registration, 1977 (Box 17)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Summer Workshop Registration, 1977 (Box 17)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Summer Workshop Registration, 1977 (Box 17)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Summer Workshop Registration, 1978 (Box 17)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Summer Workshop Registration, 1978 (Box 17)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Summer Workshop Registration, 1978 (Box 17)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Summer Workshop Registration, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Summer Workshop Registration, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Summer Workshop Registration, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Summer Workshop Registration, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Summer Workshop Registration, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Summer Workshop Registration, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Summer Workshop Registration, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Summer Workshop Registration, 1980 (Box 17)
  - AIS/DC CRMI Travel File, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - AIS/Dance Component, Memo's to Reg. Coors. And Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - Education Panel, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - AIS Panel Mtg, South Bend, Indiana, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - AIS Dance Company, Dance Movement Specialist Statements, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - AIS, ESAA, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - Assistant Dance Movement Specialists Contract File, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - Dance Movement Specialist Contracts File, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - Assistant Dance Movement Specialists, Resume and Social Security Number, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - In-School Coordinators' Info Sheet, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - Alaska, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - Arizona, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - California, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - Connecticut (carried over to 1974-1975 program), 1973-1974 (Box 18)
  - Delaware, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - Florida, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - Hawaii, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - Illinois, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - Iowa, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - Maine, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - Maryland, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - Massachusetts, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - Minnesota, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - AIS Panel Mtg. Materials Prepared for CR, Feb. 12, 1977 (Box 19)
  - Panel Materials to be Sorted and Notes to be Typed (Box 19)
  - CR-Panel Materials (Box 19)
  - Information, AIS Components (other than dance) (Box 19)
  - Artists In the Schools: Printed Materials (Box 19)
  - Visual Artists and Craftsmen In Schools, Sept. 1979 (Box 19)
  - Untitled Binder (Box 19)
  - AIS Unemployment Claims (Box 19)
  - AIS Films (Box 19)
  - Artists in Schools, 1978 (Box 19)
  - Mime, Where it Belongs in AIS (Box 19)
  - Legal File, Halloran vs. (Box 19)
  - AIS/Dance Component, Minnesota, Sue Halloran's Suit (Box 19)
  - Solo Dancers (Box 19)
  - Review Process, Application Announcement and New Application, Notes for Mar. 1980 Mtg., 1980-1981 (Box 19)
  - Review Panel Mtg., Mar. 17, 1980 (Box 19)
  - Funding Priorities, NEA Guidelines, 1979-1980 (Box 19)
  - National Endowment for the Arts and Department of Education, Correspondence/Call Reports (Box 19)
  - AIS/DC Guidelines, 1978-1979 (Box 19)
  - NEA/AIS Advisory Panel, 1979-1980 (Box 19)
  - AIS Guidelines, June 22, 1978, 1979-1980 (Box 19)
  - AIS Guidelines, National Endowment for the Arts, 1980-1981 (Box 19)
  - Contact Sheets and Schedules, 1977-1978 (Box 19)
  - Jacques d' Amboise (Box 19)
  - University of Illinois Evaluation, AIS/Dance Component (Box 19)
  - AIS Handbook, All Components, Vangie Piper, Coordinator (Box 19)
  - Misc. Memos to SAA's (Memo on Site Selection) (Box 19)
  - AIS/DTP Crossover (Box 19)
  - Possible Assistants for AIS/DC (Box 19)
  - AIS Directories, File Copies, 1978-1979 (Box 20)
  - AIS Directory, Printing Information, 1978-1979 (Box 20)
  - AIS/DC Directory, Correspondence/Mailings (Box 20)
  - AIS/Dance Component, Dance Co, Info and Resumes not in Directory, 1978-1979 (Box 20)
  - AIS Directory, Notes on Special Cases/Verification Home City Fees, 1978-1979 (Box 20)
  - AIS Directory, Xerox of Originals to Printer, 1978-1979 (Box 20)
  - AIS/DC Directory, Directory, 1978-1979 (Box 20)
  - AIS Directory, Printing Information, 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - AIS/DC Directory, Draft and Approved Copy from NEA, 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - AIS Directory, Correspondence/Mailings, 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - AIS Directory, Office Copies, 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - AIS Directory Originals, 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - AIS Directory, Office Copies, 1976-1977 (Box 20)
  - DTP Coordinator Mailing List (Box 20)
  - Artists in Schools, 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - DTP Meetings, Fall, 1974 (Box 20)
  - DTP Meetings, Fall, Preparation Files/Hotel/Meeting Spaces, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Press Photography by Jack Mitchell (Box 20)
  - DTP Meetings, Notes and Reports, Dec. 1975 (Box 20)
  - DTP Report (Box 20)
  - Expenses/Reimbursements, DTP Pre-Planning Mtg, May 7, 1976 (Box 20)
  - DTP Planning Meeting, Notes, May 7, 1976 (Box 20)
  - DTP Mtg at SW, Planning, Consultants, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 20)
  - DTP SW, 1976 (Box 20)
  - DTP, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Reimbursements, DTP Mtgs, Fall, 1976 (Box 20)
  - DTP Payments, SW, 1977 (Box 20)
  - Preparation and Notes for Fall Co. Meeting, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Printed Material for DTP Mtgs for Michael Bretman/Brian Looker, 1976 (Box 20)
  - DTP Mtg Report, Nov. 7-10, 1976 (Box 20)
  - NYC, Nov. 7-9, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Chicago, 1976 (Box 20)
  - SP, 1976 (Box 20)
  - DTP Planning Meeting Notes, Apr. 25, 1977 (Box 20)
  - DTP Planning Meeting, Suggestions from the Field, Apr. 25, 1977 (Box 20)
  - DTP Planning Meeting, Apr. 25, 1977 (Box 20)
  - CRMI Correspondence, 1972 (Box 21)
  - Charles Reinhart General Correspondence, 1973 (Box 21)
  - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 21)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 21)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Dance Touring Program General Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 21)
  - DTP Guidelines, FY, 1977 (Box 21)
  - Endowment Guidelines, FY, 1976 (Box 21)
  - CRMI Denmark (Box 21)
  - Martha Graham and Dance Company (Box 21)
  - Charles Reinhart Travel (Box 21)
  - CRMI, Travel Agency For The Arts (Box 21)
  - Dance Fund (Box 21)
  - Dance Managers Meeting, Jan. 16, 1970 (Box 21)
  - Dance/LA (Box 21)
  - Laura Dean (Box 21)
  - High School Internships (Box 21)
  - Robin Howard, The Place (Box 21)
  - Pictures, Brochures, Etc. from "The Place" (Box 21)
  - Bella Lewitzky (Box 21)
  - Don McDonagh, Dance Enclyc. (Box 21)
  - Jack Mitchell (Box 21)
  - Meredith Monk (Box 21)
  - Netherlands Dance Theatre (Box 21)
  - Alwin Nikolais (Box 21)
  - Bruce Sagan (Box 21)
  - Shanta Rao, John Coast (Box 21)
  - Shanta Rao, John Coast (Box 21)
  - Requests to Foundations and Backers for Paul Taylor (Box 21)
  - Twyla Tharp and Dancers (Box 21)
  - Charles Weidman and His Dance Theatre (Box 21)
  - Charles Weidman and His Dance Theatre (Box 21)
  - Performing Arts Management, City Center American Dance Season, Spring '70, Paul Taylor Dance Company; Shanto Rao; Brooklyn Academy of Music Festival of Dance, Printed Materials, Promotional Brochures, 1964-1970 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Management, Le Groupe de la Place Royale, Press and Publicity Materials, Press Kit, 1968 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Management, Meredith Monk/The House, Printed Materials, Promotional Brochure, 1969 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Management, Don Redlich Dance Company, Press and Publicity: Press Release (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Management, Paul Taylor Dance Company, Printed Materials, Ticket Forms, 1965 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Management, Paul Taylor Dance Company, Printed Materials, Brochures, circa 1965-circa 1970 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Management, Publicity, Paul Taylor Dance Company. Printed Materials, Returned, 1964 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Management, Paul Taylor Dance Company. Printed Materials, Brochures, 1968 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Management, Paul Taylor Dance Company. Printed Materials, Brochures, 1967 (Box 22)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company, Brochures, 1964 (Box 22)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company, Playbill, 1965 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Management, Paul Taylor Dance Company, Printed Materials, programs (in Spanish), 1965 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Management, Paul Taylor Dance Company, Hammamet (Tunisia), Printed Materials, Festival Program; Schedule, 1966 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Management, Paul Taylor Dance Company, Printed Materials, Playbills, Dec. 26-31, 1966 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Management, Paul Taylor Dance Company, Printed Materials, Playbills,, Dec. 21, 23, 26, 1967 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Management, Paul Taylor Dance Company, Printed Materials, Playbills, May 6-11, 1969 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Management, Paul Taylor Dance Company, Printed Materials, Playbills, May 5-10, 1970 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Management, Paul Taylor Dance Company, Press and Publicity, Press Coverage, 1961, 1963, 1965 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Management, Paul Taylor Dance Company, Press and Publicity Materials, Press Release, 1964 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Management, Paul Taylor Dance Company, Press Coverage, 1963, 1965-1967 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Management, Paul Taylor Dance Company, Press Coverage, Holland, 1966-1968 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Management, Paul Taylor, Awards and Tributes Programs, 16th Capezio Dance Award, 1967 (Box 22)
  - Project Management, Dance Touring Program Correspondence, 1967 (Box 22)
  - Project Management, Dance Touring Program, Dance Theatre of Harlem, Inc., Correspondence; Building Design Plot, 1971 (Box 22)
  - Project Management, Dance Touring Program, Dance in Depth, (Harper Theater Dance Festival Promotional Brochure; Newspaper Clipping, 1967-1968 (Box 22)
  - Project Management, Dance Touring Program, Dance in Depth, Technical Requirement Sheets, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
  - Tennessee, 1980-1981 (Box 22)
  - Tennessee, Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 22)
  - Utah, 1981-1982 (Box 22)
  - Virgin Islands, 1980-1981 (Box 22)
  - Virgin Islands, Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 22)
  - Wisconsin, 1980-1981 (Box 22)
  - Wisconsin, Phone Calls, 1980-1981 (Box 22)
  - Untitled Folder (Box 22)
  - Nevada State Council on the Arts Newsletter, Winter, 1980 (Box 22)
  - Mid Atlantic Regional Performing Arts Touring Program, Sept. 1981-Aug. 1982 (Box 22)
  - Non-Participating States (Box 22)
  - Artists Call Reports (Box 22)
  - Artists Correspondence (Box 22)
  - State Arts Agency Coordination, 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Mailing List and Contact Sheets (School Folks), 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Calendars, 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Coordinator's Information Sheets, 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Coordinator's Information Sheets, Western States, 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Residency Info Sheets, Resumes, Etc., 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Phone Calls, Alabama (Box 22)
  - Alabama, 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Phone Calls, Arizona (Box 22)
  - Arizona, 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Evaluation of the Mesa Artist-In Schools Program, 1974-1975 (Box 22)
  - Phone Calls, California (Box 22)
  - California, 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Phone Calls, Connecticut (Box 22)
  - Connecticut, 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - AIS and Connecticut (Box 22)
  - Phone Calls, Delaware (Box 22)
  - Delaware, 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Phone Calls, Florida (Box 22)
  - Florida, 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Florida, 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Hawaii, 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Phone Calls, Hawaii (Box 23)
  - Illinois, 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Phone Calls, Illinois (Box 23)
  - Indiana, 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Phone Calls, Indiana (Box 23)
  - Phone Calls, Iowa (Box 23)
  - Iowa, 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Phone Calls, Kentucky (Box 23)
  - Kentucky, 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Louisiana, 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Phone Calls, Louisiana (Box 23)
  - Phone Calls, Maine (Box 23)
  - Maine, 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Massachusetts, 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Phone Calls, Massachusettes (Box 23)
  - Michigan, 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Michigan, 1978 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence, NEA, Jan. 1-June 30, 1974 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence, NEA, 1973-1974 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence, Dance Movement Specialists, 1973 (Box 23)
  - State Arts Council (Box 23)
  - In-School Coordinators, 1973-1974 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence, Dance Company Corres., 1973-1974 (Box 23)
  - General Correspondence (Box 23)
  - Correspondence, NEA, 1972-1973 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence, NEA, Jan. 1-June 30, 1975 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence, NEA, July 1-Dec. 30, 1974 (Box 23)
  - In-School Coordinators Correspondence/Memorandums, 1974-1975 (Box 23)
  - Artists in Schools General Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 23)
  - Movement Specialists, 1974-1975 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence, NEA, July 1-Dec. 30, 1975 (Box 23)
  - AIS/DC General Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
  - Dance Movement Spec. Assts., 1975-1976 (Box 23)
  - In-School Coordinators Correspondence/Memos (no info sheet), 1975-1976 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence, DMS and Dance Companies, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
  - AIS/DC Memos to SED's and SAA's, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
  - Dance Company Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
  - Dance Movement Specialists File (Correspondence and Memos), 1975-1976 (Box 23)
  - AIS/DC Endowment Correspondence, Jan. 1, 1977- June 30, 1977 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence, NEA, July 1-Dec. 30, 1976 (Box 23)
  - AIS/DC Correspondence, General Correspondence, 1977 (Box 23)